{
    "subject": "resource/Dominion_of_Newfoundland",
    "predicate": "ontology/currency",
    "object": "resource/Newfoundland_dollar",
    "human_readable": "The currency of Dominion of Newfoundland is Newfoundland dollar.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9723953604698181,
            "question": "What is the currency of the Dominion of Newfoundland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9192507266998291,
            "question": "What type of dollar was used in the Dominion of Newfoundland?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8853374719619751,
            "question": "When did the Dominion of Newfoundland use its own currency?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8496217727661133,
            "question": "Was the Newfoundland dollar a separate currency?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7711391448974609,
            "question": "What other currencies were used in Newfoundland before the Newfoundland dollar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7235947847366333,
            "question": "What is the historical significance of the Newfoundland dollar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6980975270271301,
            "question": "Are there any remnants of the Newfoundland dollar today?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6903125047683716,
            "question": "Were there any unique features of the Newfoundland dollar?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5458451509475708,
            "question": "How did the Newfoundland dollar compare to other Canadian currencies at the time?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5056958198547363,
            "question": "What happened to the Newfoundland dollar after Confederation with Canada?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The currency of Dominion of Newfoundland is Newfoundland dollar.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9201_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=How did the Newfoundland dollar compare to other Canadian currencies at the time?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9201_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Were there any unique features of the Newfoundland dollar?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9201_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any remnants of the Newfoundland dollar today?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9201_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9201_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9201_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9201_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9201_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9201_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9201_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9201_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9201_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9201_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9201_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the currency used in the Dominion of Newfoundland, stating that it was the Newfoundland dollar. Therefore, the statement \"The currency of Dominion of Newfoundland is Newfoundland dollar\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}